We're screwed! Pants, pants, some pants, pants!
It's not fair!
We had twice ze flavor.
[Screams of agony]
I got out of there just in time.
And I got the usual reception.
Abe! Abe! It's Abe! It's Abey!
It's Abe! It's that Abe guy!
The Mudokons were slowly coming together.
And they were using using their skills to build something new.
Ah!
D'oww!
That gotta hurt!
You'll be fine. Get along would ya.
See it's all feeling better already.
Hello, my name is Alf.
Hi Alf!
I had my first brew
while I was with Abe in the desert.
Well....
They were taking things one step at a time.
Can I share now?
No, just shut up!
All was going well.
But we knew, there had to be more of us out there.
We're screwed...
And we're gonna find them!
We interrupt this program to bring you this special news bulletin.
Rumor Kontrol reports, that Abe
the terrorist mastermind behind the destruction of RuptureFarms
is also behind the SoulStorm Brewery atrocity.
I hate that guy!
Stay tuned for more on this story as it develops!
This message brought to you by:
And don't even think about running it on your measly 32 bit system!